// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " I could answer only …………………… questions.",
    answer: "a few",
    options: [ "few", "a few","little","a little" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "We haven’t got ………………… money.",
    answer: "much",
    options: ["many","much of","much","none of these"]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question:"He doesn’t have ………………… patience.",
    answer: "much",
    options: [
      "many", "much","most","more" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " …………………… them approved the plan.",
    answer: "Many of",
    options: ["Much", "Much of","Many","Many of" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " You ask too ………………………… questions.",
    answer: "many ",
    options: [ "much", "much of","many","many of" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "……………………… time is required to learn a new language.",
    answer: "Much",
    options: ["Many", "Much","Much of","little"  ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Bullying is a problem that affects ……………………… children.",
    answer: "many",
    options: [ "many", "much","little","much of" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "I have had …………………… ups and downs in my life.",
    answer: "many",
    options: [ "much", "many","most","little" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "We are very ………………………. obliged for your assistance.",
    answer: "much",
    options: [ "much", "much of","many","many of " ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "He spends ……………………. his time reading.",
    answer: "much of",
    options: [  "much", "much of","many of","many"  ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: " I didn’t do ……………………. work yesterday.",
    answer: "much",
    options: [  "much", "many","much of","many of" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "You didn’t eat ………………………",
    answer: "much",
    options: [  "much", "many","many of","much of" ]
  },
];